so I think tadalfil um tadalfil I think
is actually a really really good
medication um I think for guys who are
experiencing any erectile dysfunction
for guys who have um any cardiovascular
disease as well this is a really great
medication um I also urge caution with
um just treating erectile dysfunction
with tadal because I always talk about
this the holy Triant when it comes to
erectile function and just thinking
about essentially brain brain and nerve
issues so are you stressed um you know
um do you have any nerve problems um and
those are those are really things to
sort of consider then obviously hormonal
problems which obviously we'd be trying
to treat um uh as well and then vascular
issues uh you know is there a problem
from a vascular Supply do you have
vascular inflammation or um a
atherosclerotic disease as well um and
making sure you consider all of them um
and sort of ask the questions because if
one of those or more than one of those
has a problem um then you you won't
necessarily be able to wholly treat it
with a pd5 inhibitor um but I think the
benefit so some people struggle with
some side effects from toil um and they
can range from reflux so acid heartburn
um so you know you can bypass for that
by taking after food and things like
that um sometimes people get a bit of a
stuffy nose because they're causing
violet Val itation Sor throughout the
body as well so that's just something
else to look out for but and actually
taking for those people just taking a
really tiny dose of half a tablet a day
can sometimes resolve those things the
other issue that some people get
particularly if they do a lot of
training and a lot deadlifting things
can be back pump as well which is just
something else that's just really
unpleasant if you don't warn people off
about um and again for me I'll often say
to people um actually start off on half
a tablet see how you get on with it see
if you any side effects and go from
there but yeah tadalfil is definitely a
medication that I would um
recommend um if you know if any of those
um things are an issue for you
[Music]